<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
        <string-array name="list">
            <item>How to drink alcohol without losing your memory</item>
            <item>How to drink alcohol in a healthy way</item>
            <item>Wrong way to drink alcohol</item>
            <item>Manners at a drinking place</item>
            <item>Manners when drinking wine</item>
            <item>How to drink a cocktail</item>
            <item>How to drink champagne</item>
        </string-array>

        <string-array name="list1_1">
            <item>\n Have a simple meal before drinking.</item>
            <item>Drink slowly.</item>
            <item>Avoid one shot.</item>
            <item>Drink lots of water.</item>
            <item>Avoid drinking if sleep is poor or condition is poor the day before.</item>
            <item>Do not smoke when drinking alcohol.</item>
            <item>Give the liver a rest day.</item>
        </string-array>

        <string-array name="list1_2">
       <item>Drinking alcohol on an empty stomach will absorb most of the alcohol from the stomach and transmit it to the stomach acid. However, if there is food in the stomach, it goes down to the intestines and lowers the concentration and is gradually transferred to the liver. \n</item>
            <item>It is much more harmful to drink a bottle of soju within 30 minutes than to drink 2 soju slowly for 2 hours. About 10% of drinking alcohol is released by breathing, so it is good to drink while talking slowly. \n</item>
            <item>Alcohol breaks down from the liver into water and carbon dioxide. Suddenly drinking alcohol suddenly increases carbon dioxide, accelerates heart rate, blood circulation speeds up and blood pressure goes up. \n</item>
            <item>Water dilutes the alcohol in your body. In general, people with small physiology have a low blood volume, so their blood alcohol concentration increases sharply. It is helpful to drink more water before drinking to increase your fluids. \n</item>
            <item>If you are tired, you can\'t decipher the liver. Therefore, even if you drink a little, get drunk quickly.\n</item>
            <item>If you smoke, you will lose oxygen in the liver and you will not be able to decipher well. \n</item>
            <item>After one drink, leave a 3 ~ 4 day interval until you have the next drink. 72 hours after drinking, the liver returns to normal. \n</item>
        </string-array>


        <string-array name="list2_1">
            <item>\n It is appropriate to drink only 3 cups of soju three times a week.</item>
            <item>If your body is cold, it is good to drink soju, and if you have a lot of heat, it is better to drink beer.</item>
            <item>soju has pork belly, red wine is good for almond.</item>
            <item>Water is the best alcohol snack.</item>
        </string-array>

        <string-array name="list2_2">
            <item>There is a personal gap, More than 170 grams of alcohol per day is fatal in the liver. 170 g of alcohol corresponds to about two bottles of soju. Experts say that men should drink about 3 cups of soju and about 1.5 cups of women. \n</item>
            <item>Drinking snacks are mostly meat, but it is better to choose the type of meat according to the person\'s constitution. soeumin chicken, soyangin pork, taeeumin beef is good choice. \n Tofu, milk and high-protein snacks will help the liver function. Milk and cheese slow down the rate of alcohol absorption. \n</item>
            <item>soju is good for foods rich in protein such as whites, vegetables, squid and fish stew, Eating with cucumbers is helpful for diuretic action. \n There is a grain of rice in a beer. So it is easy to feel fullness. It is more suitable for foods like light fruits and high-protein tofu than calorie foods. \n
Wine is an alkaline drink, so it is accompanied by acidic dishes such as meat or cheese. \n</item>
            <item>Water dilutes the alcohol and makes it drink less. \n In some cases, they mix with carbonated beverages to make the drink taste better, but this would rather promote alcohol absorption and make them more drunk. \n</item>
        </string-array>

        <string-array name="list3_1">
            <item>\nIs it good to drink and sweat in the sauna?</item>
            <item>How about eating a placebo before drinking?</item>
            <item>Once you vomit, the alcohol sober up?</item>
            <item>If the liver function is bad, do you drink and your face gets red?</item>
            <item>Do you drink milk before and after drinking to protect your stomach? </item>
            <item>Is it bad to drink alcohol and sparkling water?</item>
            <item> If i eat a lot of snacks then be less drunk? </item>
            <item>Do you drink alcohol and your body temperature goes down?</item>
            <item>If I drink coffee, less get drunk?</item>
            <item>Do i drink a lot and not die instantly?</item>
        </string-array>

        <string-array name="list3_2" formatted="false">
            <item>X. If you think need to sweat to relieve hangovers After drinking alcohol and getting into the hot water or enjoying the sauna, the blood vessels expand and the blood rushes suddenly into the heart, which is dangerous. \n</item>
            <item>X. Because drugs and alcohol are destroyed through the liver, the liver must make enzymes that simultaneously destroy alcohol and drugs. Therefore, liver overdo oneself. Especially antacids can protect the stomach.
But it blocks the activity of the alcoholic enzymes in the stomach wall and increases blood alcohol concentration by 20%.
\n</item>
            <item>X. Alcohol is absorbed by only about 10% in the stomach and about 90% in the small intestine.\nVomiting causes the above unabsorbed alcohol to escape from the food and cause a hangover, but vomiting has a negative impact on health. \n</item>
            <item>O. The reason why we drink alcohol and have a reddened face is because we are lacking or lacking the enzyme that decomposes acetaldehyde. Acetaldehyde, also known as a highly toxic and cancer-causing substance, spreads through the blood vessels when not degraded. At this time, the blood vessels expand by toxic substances, which makes the face red and breathy. \n</item>
            <item>X. Milk is weakly alkaline and can dilute or neutralize stomach acid, which can temporarily improve heartburn symptoms, but ultimately promotes gastric acid secretion, which can make gastritis worse.\n</item>
            <item>O. If dilute the soju with carbonated water, your mouth will feel better and the alcohol level will be lower. It is easy to drink, but the diluted carbonated water works with hydrochloric acid in the stomach to stimulate gastric acid secretion by stimulating the mucous membrane.\n</item>
            <item>X. Take a slow hangover because the rate of alcohol absorption decreases because of snack. The degree of hangover is precisely proportional to the amount of alcohol consumed.\n</item>
            <item>O. Alcohol spreads to the peripheral blood vessels temporarily, but it seems that the body is warmed up. In fact, the vascular enlargement increases the heat loss, and the body temperature is lowered by suppressing the body temperature control center of the brain.\n</item>
            <item>X. When you drink coffee after drinking alcohol, caffeine acts on the central nervous system, weakening your brain\'s judgment, alleviating emotions, and making you feel confident about your physiology, such as safety, self-satisfaction and memory. However, hangovers do not resolve.\n</item>
            <item>X. Alcohol becomes acetaldehyde by alcohol dehydratase. Drinking too much can cause acetaldehyde, which is not metabolized in the body, to accumulate, which can lead to vomiting, headache, difficulty breathing, and acute death.\n</item>
        </string-array>

        <string-array name="list4_1">
            <item>\n How to sit in a drink place</item>
            <item>How to give alcohol</item>
            <item>How to fill drink</item>
            <item>How to get alcohol in a cup</item>
            <item>How to drink alcohol</item>
            <item>How to turn around a alcohol</item>
        </string-array>

        <string-array name="list4_2" formatted="false">
       <item>- The central seat in the center of the table (or wall) on the far side of the entrance is a good place to see the door.

It is where employees and other guests do not disturb.

\n-

When you sit down with several people, you are recommended to sit in order of age.
\n-

When considering the purpose and background of the place, the place to sit may vary depending on the central characteristics of the place.
\n</item>
            <item>- Older people or people with high social status first recommend glass and drinks.

\n-

You can get the boss with one hand, but if you change the drink, your right hand will normally support the floor.

\n-


You can give it to a child with one hand, but if you put the cup on the table and fill the cup, it is not manners.

\n-

If left handed, it can give a bad feeling.

\n-

When you give a cup to the upper man, hold the cup with your right hand and hold the cup under your right hand with your left hand.\n</item>
            <item>- If you are drunk with a person of the same age, grab a bottle with your right hand and follow your chest with your left hand.

\n-

 It is advisable to fill 90% of the cup properly.\n-



In the case of a kettle, hold the kettle handle with your right hand and press the lid of the kettle with your left hand.
\n- For bottled drinks, hold the bottle with your right hand and support your right wrist with your left hand. If the distance is long, put your left hand on your right chest.
\n</item>
            <item>- The cup of the boss is given with both hands politely, and if you have a cup, do not put it down, but hold it in your hands until you follow the liquor.\n-
kneels down and receives it with both hands and drinks alcohol with his upper body turned sideways. If an adult fills up.\n- It is against the courtesy to support the left hand or the chin with a drink with a younger person. The boss lightly puts his left hand on his chest.

\n- Even if you can not drink

take my first cup to show courtesy and lick my liquor.\n</item>
            <item>- If the boss follows the liquor, do not put it directly on top of it, but place it behind a sip.
\n-
When making a toast, make it higher than the boss of your boss and do not hit it high.\n</item>
            <item>- empty the cup I have received and turn the cup to the original cup owner with a sign of gratitude. \n- When a man or woman recommends alcohol, the man first recommends it to the woman, and the woman does not force it.\n</item>
        </string-array>

        <string-array name="list5_1">
            <item>\n1. If you are an invited guest, you should not be offered wine or you should stay silent.</item>
            <item>2. It is polite not to raise the cup when you follow the wine.</item>
            <item>3. Empty your mouth before drinking wine.</item>
            <item>4. When catching a wine glass, do not grab the bowl..</item>
            <item>5. Do not leave traces of fingerprints or lipstick on the wine glass. </item>
            <item>6. If you do not want to drink wine, put your finger on the glass.</item>
            <item>7. When hosting a wine, follow the woman first, then the clockwise direction. </item>
            <item>8. In order to taste and taste the wine, the amount of wine that follows the glass is also important.</item>
            <item>9. If have some wine left, you can fill it in.</item>
            <item>10. If you share a meal with wine, you should refrain from the sweet wine.</item>
        </string-array>






        <string-array name="list5_2">
            <item>It is polite for the host to recommend wine and drink as the host orders. Of course, if you are asked directly what your favorite wine is, tell your favorite wine. The same is true of drinking wine with the company\'s boss.\n</item>
            <item>Lifting a wine glass is a sign of dissatisfaction that the wine glass is not clean. To be polite, tap the wine glass base with your finger. Wine glasses are always on their right.\n</item>
            <item>If you have food in your mouth, you can not feel the true taste of wine. Before you drink wine, you can enjoy the taste of wine even more by removing the bitter taste of the mouth with a light meal such as baguette bread slices. Or drink a little water and rinse your mouth.\n</item>
            <item>If you catch the body part, the temperature of the wine will rise and it will affect the taste, so grab the neck (stem) part and drink it. \n</item>
            <item>If you eat under light, be careful because if you catch the torso, your cup may look dirty to your opponent. If you are a woman, lightly wipe your lips with a napkin before drinking wine.\n</item>
            <item>\n</item>
            <item>\n</item>
            <item>The amount of wine should be only 1/3 to 1/2 of the glass. When you follow the wine, follow the bottle so that the bubbles do not flow, then lightly turn the wine bottle. \n</item>
            <item>\n</item>
            <item>Sweet wine ruins the meal. If the other person hesitates to pick the wine, I would recommend the house wine during dinner and sweet wine after meals.\n</item>
        </string-array>

        <string-array name="list6_1">
            <item>\n1. Do not touch the glass floor to warm your hands.It is good to be cold.\n</item>
            <item>2. Do not use a straw. Just put it on the glass and drink it. If you need to use a straw, bite the tip of the lip and drink a cocktail in your mouth and drink enough.\n</item>
            <item>3. The cocktail flavor disappears after a certain period of time. We recommend 10 to 15 minutes for small glass and 20 to 30 minutes for large glass. \n</item>
            <item>4. Drinking cocktail glass should always be on the right.\n</item>
            <item>5. When drinking a cocktail, be careful not to make a slight noise by tilting the cup.\n</item>
            <item>6. Cocktails should be chosen according to taste, and if you do not have enough information, ask for advice from the bartender. It is good to choose according to fashion that day.\n</item>
            <item>7. It is courtesy to eat fruit that is decorated in a cocktail glass after eating half of a cocktail and then sharing it with the grain twice or three times. Olive seeds are wrapped in paper instead of in cocktail glass.\n</item>
            <item>8. It\'s not good to pretend cocktails.\n</item>
            <item>9. Even if you have a partner who can not drink, you can enjoy it lightly depending on the atmosphere.\n</item>
            <item>10. Cool cocktails are lightly wrapped in paper napkins to prevent dripping drops, and do not wipe their lips on paper napkins that are underneath.\n</item>
            <item>11. If you want to have another drink after you\'ve finished drinking, ask for the same thing you just drank.\n</item>
        </string-array>

        <string-array name="list7_1">
            <item>\n1. Champagne is soaked in an ice bucket 30 minutes before drinking, when it cools to about 5 to 8 degrees.\n</item>
            <item>2. Cover the bottle with a napkin, then use the end of a cloth to fasten the stopper, loosen the wire, and remove the stopper.\n</item>
            <item>3. Do not follow to the end of the drink, but only about 60% of the cup.\n</item>
            <item>4. When the bubble is too much, it fills up a little, rests and fills it.\n</item>
        </string-array>


    </resources>